[Music]
it shows 30,000 sad faces one for each
employee she fired between 1999 and 2005
I haven't heard numbers that Grim since
the count got hooked on
meth sorry it's sad it happened don't
blame the
messenger one two three bags of drugs if
you want to be a Brooklyn girl you in
Brooklyn get a Brooklyn hat got to get a
Brooklyn hat I get a Net's hat a Net's
hat comeing bu some socks the back $5
this Clinton right here all day Bill
going to like these on her in the middle
of the night in the White House and yes
every 28 days I bed but the country went
on you know I mean you know it's like
there plenty of women in the White House
who I mean and we have had women as
National Security advisers yeah listen
this go ahead this is your topic tell me
about the bleeding every I just saying
lar Larry I'm bleeding right now and
it's so everything is F and you're
speaking Larry Wilmore here if you like
the nightly show on Comedy Central like
us on Facebook too just don't poke me I
do not like being poked you can Candy
Crush me